<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><NewsFeed><NewsItem><Title>‘Over 2,000 projects still pending in AJK after 2005 earthquake’</Title><Description>The devastating earthquake claimed more than 70,000 lives in 2005</Description><PublishedDate>10/8/2019 4:36:09 PM +00:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SamaaTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>ACE arrests CEO of fake housing society in Karachi</Title><Description>The society was built on encroached government land in Nooriabad</Description><PublishedDate>10/8/2019 4:18:09 PM +00:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SamaaTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Pakistan wants to expand economic cooperation with China: foreign minister</Title><Description>Says his government wishes more investments in the country</Description><PublishedDate>10/8/2019 3:29:41 PM +00:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SamaaTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>IHC fixes petition against JUI-F’s Islamabad march for hearing</Title><Description>IHC Chief Justice Athar Minallah will conduct hearing on Wednesday</Description><PublishedDate>10/8/2019 3:06:28 PM +00:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SamaaTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>AQIS leader Asim Umar killed in Helmand, says Afghan intelligence</Title><Description>He was an Indian national</Description><PublishedDate>10/8/2019 2:24:15 PM +00:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SamaaTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Team in need of more match-winners, says Misbah</Title><Description>Pakistan head coach terms Sri Lanka series defeat an 'eye-opener'</Description><PublishedDate>10/8/2019 2:09:29 PM +00:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SamaaTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>SBCA to establish special courts to deal with illegal constructions</Title><Description>It's only awaiting an approval by the Sindh government</Description><PublishedDate>10/8/2019 1:53:15 PM +00:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SamaaTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Shamoon Abbasi requests censor board to review his ‘Durj’ again</Title><Description>It was scheduled to release in Pakistan on October 18</Description><PublishedDate>10/8/2019 12:40:57 PM +00:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SamaaTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Women protest power cuts, water shortage in Quetta</Title><Description>They blame the outages on QESCO's negligence</Description><PublishedDate>10/8/2019 12:28:42 PM +00:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SamaaTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Mehwish Hayat’s dance rehearsal video triggers moral police</Title><Description>The actor fires back at her haters</Description><PublishedDate>10/8/2019 12:11:49 PM +00:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SamaaTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Sri Lanka clinch T20I series as Pakistan’s experi-mental approach backfires</Title><Description>A blend of questionable team selection, a familiar middle-order collapse and generally lethargic play saw Pakistan lose to Sri Lanka by 35 runs in the second T20I at the Gaddafi Stadium Lahore on Monday.
The result saw Sri Lanka take an unassailable 2-0 lead in the three-match series. It was the inexperienced islanders' first-ever win over Pakistan in a bilateral T20I series.
Pakistan innings
The hosts' innings was dealt two early setbacks when they first lost Fakhar Zaman (6) and then Babar Azam, the world's top-ranked T20I batsman, for just three runs.
Captain Sarfaraz, not for the first time in the series, came in at two-down with the responsibility on his shoulders to bail the team out in a difficult run chase. On the other end was Ahmed Shehzad — another in desperate need of some runs.
This time, however, Sarfaraz was looking in much better touch, signified by a four and a six on back-to-back balls in the 6th over.
The eighth over proved a nightmare for Pakistan batsmen, and it pretty much decided the fate of the match and the series.
Shehzad, picked in the side despite intense criticism, disappointed again, dancing down the track against Wanindu Hasaranga and getting bowled out.
Umar Akmal was out lbw the very next ball and captain Sarfaraz followed the duo back in the pavilion a ball later.
The sequence of three wickets in four balls by Hasaranga meant that Sri Lanka tightened their grip on the match as well as the series.
At this point Asif Ali and Imad Wasim were at the crease. Things could have gone really ugly for the hosts but the duo batted responsibly and put together a 50-run partnership from nowhere. There was still a lot to be done though as the run rate had skyrocketed into double figures.
Imad's impressive 29-ball 47-run knock concluded when he, after hitting a couple of cheeky fours, missed one and was adjudged out lbw.
Sri Lanka innings
Earlier, the in-form Danushka Gunathilaka and Avishka Fernando opened the innings for Sri Lanka, whereas Imad Wasim and Mohammad Amir shared the new ball for the hosts.
Gunathilaka was again looking in the mood, hitting several boundaries early on. But Wasim struck in the 3rd over, having the leftie nick one back to Sarfaraz Ahmed. He contributed 15 this time.
The loss of their star batsman did not seem to bother the visitors who kept on finding boundaries. However, Fernando and newcomer Bhanuka Rajapaksa's promising looking partnership was broken in the 5th over when the former attempted a run against the gazelle-like Shadab Khan, who hit the bulls eyes. Sri Lanka were 41-2 at the end of a quarter of their overs.
Needlessly risky runs were a constant theme in the first few overs and Pakistan could have had another run out, had all their fielders been like Shadab.
Rajapaksa and Shehan Jayasuriya made sure that no further wickets were lost in the next five, taking the score to 80-2 at the end of 10 overs.
The hard-hitting Rajapaksa brought up his 50 off just 31 balls in the 12th over. He kept on pounding the Pakistani bowlers and had his side eyeing 200.
The 94-run stand between the two was finally broken in the 15th over when Asif Ali ran out Jayasuriya.
Rajapaksa (77) was caught in extra cover before Sri Lanka lost another to a run-out — the innings' third till that point.
While the Lankans couldn't surpass the 200-run mark, captain Dasun Shanaka's 27-run cameo helped Sri Lanka finish with 182-6 in their allotted 20 overs.
Pre-match chatter
Umar Akmal and Ahmed Shehzad were retained despite their failure with the bat in the opening match.
Iftikhar Ahmed and Faheem Ashraf were replaced by Fakhar Zaman and Wahab Riaz.
Sri Lanka did not make any changes to the line-up that pretty much outclassed the hosts by 64 runs in the first T20 in Lahore on Saturday.
Playing XIs 
Pakistan: Fakhar Zaman, Ahmed Shehzad, Babar Azam, Umar Akmal, Sarfaraz Ahmed(capt&amp;amp;wk), Asif Ali, Imad Wasim, Wahab Riaz, Shadab Khan, Mohammad Amir, Mohammad Hasnain
Sri Lanka: Danushka Gunathilaka, Avishka Fernando, Bhanuka Rajapaksa, Dasun Shanaka(capt), Shehan Jayasuriya, Isuru Udana, Wanindu Hasaranga, Minod Bhanuka(wk), Lakshan Sandakan, Kasun Rajitha, Nuwan Pradeep</Description><PublishedDate>10/7/2019 8:15:23 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Mohammad Hasnain becomes youngest bowler to claim hat-trick in T20I cricket</Title><Description>Pakistan fast bowler Mohammad Hasnain on Saturday became the youngest bowler in cricket history to claim a T20I hat trick.
The 19-year-old pacer achieved the feat against Sri Lanka in the first of the three-match T20I series against Sri Lanka.
He picked up a wicket on the final ball of the 16th over and two more on the first two balls of the 19th over.
The disconnect between the first and other two wickets meant that his feat was largely lost on the crowd and even the commentary team.
It was only after he had completed his hat-trick, it dawned that he has three in three balls.
Hasnain finished with figures of 3-37 in his four overs. Although he was wayward at the start, he came back strong and made his wicket-taking ability erase most of what had happened earlier.</Description><PublishedDate>10/5/2019 10:57:24 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Messi denies conflict with Barcelona after Inter victory</Title><Description>Lionel Messi insisted on Wednesday there are no problems between him and Antoine Griezmann or between the players and Barcelona´s board.
Messi returned from injury to make his second start of the season against Inter Milan in the Champions League as Barca came from behind to win 2-1.
Speaking after the match, Messi was asked about his relationship with Griezmann, who had said on Tuesday it was "difficult" to establish a connection with the Argentine while he had been injured.
"Obviously we have no problem," Messi said. "There is a good relationship with everyone, the dressing room is united. We needed this victory and hopefully now we can kick on and continue in this way."
Luis Suarez scored a sensational double at Camp Nou and it was Messi that supplied the Uruguayan´s 85th-minute winner, with a pass at the end of a weaving run down the right.
Barcelona now sit level on four points with Borussia Dortmund in Group F.
There have also been suggestions of a rift between Barcelona´s players and the board, with Gerard Pique implying last weekend that articles critical of the team had come from higher up the club, however Messi denied the relationship had soured
"We are fine. The important thing is to talk about the triumph of today and against Getafe," he said.
"We have Sevilla now to finish well before the international break. We will try to win it because it creates a mess when there is no football so we want to finish well and go out on a high before the break."</Description><PublishedDate>10/3/2019 11:11:24 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Pakistan defeat Sri Lanka by five wickets in third ODI</Title><Description>Pakistan defeated Sri Lanka by five wickets in the third and final day-night international between the two sides in Karachi on Wednesday, taking the three-match series 2-0.
Sri Lanka were lifted to 297-9 in their 50 overs opener Danushka Gunathilaka scoring a career best 133 before Pakistan reached their target in 48.2 overs.
Fakhar Zaman led the way with 76 while fellow opener Abid Ali scored 74 and Haris Sohail 56.
Pakistan won the second game by 67 runs while the first match was rained off without a ball being bowled, both in Karachi.
Pakistan were off to a good chase before the first wicket fell at 19.3 overs, when Abid Ali (74 off 67) was dismissed off a googly by Hasaranga.
Babar Azam (31 off 26) who was ruled 'out' after a successful leg-before-wicket review appeal of Pradeep's delivery at 29.1 overs.
Fakhar Zaman (76 off 91) was the next man out, who in an attempt to hit an upper cut, ended up hitting it towards the third man fielder (Shanaka) and was caught out.
Earlier, Gunathilaka knocked a 134-ball 133 with 16 boundaries and a six for his second hundred which lifted Sri Lanka after they won the toss and batted on a flat National stadium pitch.
Gunathilaka, suspended twice for breaches of disciplines in the last two years, held the innings together with stands of 88 with skipper Lahiru Thirimanne (36) for the second, 50 for the third with Angelo Perera (13) and 74 with debutant Minod Bhanuka (36) for the fourth in a brilliant display of batting.
He was finally dismissed in the 45th over, bowled by paceman Mohammad Amir who was the best Pakistani bowler with 3-50.
It was Amir who gave Pakistan an early breakthrough when he had Avishka Fernando caught behind for four by Sarfaraz Ahmed, leading the Green Shirts for the 50th time in an ODI.
Gunathilaka defied Pakistan's bowling with guts and determination, improving his previous ODI best of 116 he made against Zimbabwe at Hambantota in 2017.
Thirimanne hit four boundaries off 54 balls while Bhanuka had two sixes in his 39-ball knock.
All-rounder Dasun Shanaka hit a quick 24-ball 43 with five boundaries and two sixes as Sri Lanka added 50 in the last five overs.
Pakistan, who lead the three-match series 1-0 on winning the second match by 67 runs, brought Abid Ali and Mohammad Nawaz for Imam-ul-Haq and Imad Wasim.
For Sri Lanka, Sadeera Samarawickrama, Isuru Udana and Oshada Fernando made way for Bhanuka, Lakshan Sandakan and Perera.
The first match was rained off, also in Karachi, on Friday.
After the ODIs conclude, the teams will face each other in three Twenty20 internationals in Lahore.
Teams:
Sri Lanka: Lahiru Thirimanne (capt), Danushka Gunathilaka, Avishka Fernando, Angelo Perera, Minod Bhanuka (wk), Shehan Jayasuriya, Dasun Shanaka, Wanindu Hasaranga, Lakshan Sandakan, Lahiru Kumara, Nuwan Pradeep
Pakistan: Fakhar Zaman, Abid Ali, Babar Azam, Haris Sohail, Iftikhar Ahmed, Sarfaraz Ahmed (capt &amp;amp; wk), Mohammad Nawaz, Shadab Khan, Wahab Riaz, Mohammad Amir, Usman Shinwari</Description><PublishedDate>10/2/2019 1:55:44 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Babar Azam becomes fastest Pakistani to 1,000 runs in a calendar year</Title><Description>Pakistan’s flamboyant batsman Babar Azam on Monday completed 1,000 runs in the calendar year 2019 to become the first Pakistani batsman to reach the milestone since 2013.
Azam reached this milestone in the 19th inning of the year making him the fastest batsman from Pakistan to complete 1,000 runs in any calendar year.
He achieved this feat just as he completed his 54th run during Pakistan’s second ODI against Sri Lanka here at the National Stadium.
The right-handed batsman is the 10th Pakistani batsman overall to score one thousand runs in ODIs in a calendar year, and the first since 2013.
The duo of Misbah ul Haq and Mohammad Hafeez had scored 1,000 ODI runs (Misbah 1,373 and Hafeez 1,301) in 2013.
Since then, Pakistan batsmen had to wait for six years to reach this milestone.
Mohammad Yousuf of Pakistan has the most feats of 1,000 calendar year runs in ODIs by the fact that he achieved it on three different occasions, in 2000, 2002 and 2003.
Aamir Sohail, Ijaz Ahmed, Inzamam ul Haq and Hafeez have also achieved this feat twice while Javed Miandad, Misbah-ul-Haq, Saeed Anwar and Younis Khan reached this milestone just once in past.
Babar, 24, has already recorded several Pakistan’s ODI records to his name. He is considered as one of the best white ball players of recent days.
Babar Azam reaches the milestone in 19th inning of the year which makes him fastest from Pakistan to complete 1000 runs in any calendar year.</Description><PublishedDate>10/1/2019 7:29:20 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Pakistan’s Shadab Khan all fired up to become regular all-rounder</Title><Description>Pakistan’s young cricketer Shadab Khan said Sunday he has set his eyes on becoming a regular all-rounder in the national cricket team.
Speaking to media here in the country's southern port city, Shadab said he was working hard on his batting to be able to serve the team in all capacities.
The spinner — who fast-tracked himself to the Pakistan team after a remarkable performance in the Pakistan Super League (PSL) 2017 — noted: "I have been working hard on my batting as I am to be an all-rounder for the team.
"I am looking forward to do that in next two matches here. I am ready to bat any position, at any number where my team wants me to bat in order."
The cricketer acknowledged his inability to perform to his fans' expectations recently in white-ball cricket but promised that he would do better in the series against Sri Lanka.
“I know that I haven’t done too good recently. But my role is an attacking spinner and cricket has changed recently, so I would be happy even if I go with figures of three for 50 in an ODI,” he said, highlighting that his economy rate in white-ball cricket was not that bad.
“I don’t know how the wicket would be but I hope it will have some support for spinners,” Shadab said, hoping for doing something good in front of home crowd.
He added that the young Sri Lankan team should not be underestimated. “They have something to prove and they’ll give their best.
"I know few of them from my U19 playing days and A team’s tour and I am aware of their strengths. It will be good series with them,” he emphasised.</Description><PublishedDate>9/29/2019 10:22:25 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>First ODI between Pakistan, Sri Lanka called off due to heavy rain</Title><Description>The first one-day international match between Pakistan and Sri Lanka that was supposed to take place on Friday was called off due to heavy rain in Karachi.
The Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB) has announced a complete refund for tickets under international rules, as the heavy rain made it impossible for even the toss to take place.
According to officials, the cut-off time for the match (the time till when the match can be delayed as per rules) was 8:30pm, but it was called off at 4:30pm as it became clear that it would be impossible for staff to drain out rainwater dumped onto the field by a massive thunderstorm that struck a couple of hours before the match was due to start.
The rain water affected the pitch as well as the field in the stadium, officials said.
The second ODI will be played in the National Stadium Karachi on Sunday.
This was the first time a match was called off in the stadium due to rain. The stadium has hosted 47 matches since 1980.</Description><PublishedDate>9/27/2019 5:17:47 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Misbahul Haq is not expected to make major changes to Pakistan's playing eleven</Title><Description>Pakistan cricket team may have a new head coach in place but it’s playing eleven against Sri Lanka will reportedly be quite similar to how it was in World Cup 2019.
The Pakistani innings, as was the case during the World Cup, will be opened by Fakhar Zaman and Imamul Haq neither of which had a stellar World Cup campaign, and the former of which endured a torrid 2018-19 season.
Babar Azam will purportedly bat at one-down position, followed by Haris Sohail. The biggest surprise, perhaps, comes in the form of the batting order, with head coach Misbahul Haq having assigned the number five slot for captain Sarfaraz Ahmed.
The skipper had at times been accused of hiding behind his teammates when the going gets tough, but the new head coach seems adamant on addressing that by promoting Sarfaraz up the order.
Coming after captain Sarfaraz will be recalled batsman Iftikhar Ahmed — one of the two changes in store.
The spin bowling all-rounders’ spots will continue to be occupied by Imad Wasim and Shadab Khan, whereas Mohammad Amir, Wahab Riaz and Usman Shinwari will split fast bowling duties.
Shinwari will be the like-for-like replacement of Shaheen Shah Afridi, who has been rested for the series after contracting dengue virus during the off-season.</Description><PublishedDate>9/26/2019 11:59:24 AM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Faheem Ashraf joins Imad, Shadab in top 10 T20I bowlers ranking</Title><Description>Pakistani paceman Faheem Ashraf on Wednesday broke into the ICC's top 10 T20I ranking for bowlers, becoming the third Pakistani bowler to be currently on the list.
Faheem Ashraf joined compatriots Imad Wasim and Shadab Khan, who currently stand on second and third position respectively.
Another Afghanistan spinner makes it to the top 10!@Mujeeb_R88 has jumped 29 places to No.9 in the latest @MRFWorldwide ICC Men's T20I Ranking for bowlers. pic.twitter.com/upJdPbEuej
— ICC (@ICC) September 25, 2019
Simultaneously, Afghanistan's Mujeeb ur Rahman also made it to the list of T20I bowling elites.
After being announced as the 10th best T20I bowler, Ashraf took to social media and engaged in friendly banter with teammate Shadab Khan.
Ashraf tagged Shadab and said: "My brother, beware! I'm coming after you. I'm in form, my friend, and I'm bowling very fast these days."
Shadab tweeted back, saying: "No worries, brother! My 'googly' is also landing in the right areas :) I have my eyes on the number 1 spot. You're still far away, my brother, you have a lot of work to do!"</Description><PublishedDate>9/25/2019 10:58:58 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Sri Lankan cricket team take off for Pakistan</Title><Description>Sri Lanka's depleted national cricket squad left for Pakistan on Tuesday expressing confidence in security promises by the hosts despite reports that the team could be targeted by militants.
The Sri Lanka team were attacked in Lahore in 2009. Since then most international teams have refused to tour the South Asian country, leaving Pakistan to play nearly all their "home" games in the United Arab Emirates.
Ten senior players citing security concerns have opted out of the tour comprising three one-day internationals and three T20 matches beginning on Friday.
But the captain of the T20 squad, Dasun Shanaka, said Tuesday he had no misgivings about returning to Pakistan after they played a T20 international in Lahore in October 2017, their first since the 2009 attack.
"I have been there before," Shanaka told reporters just before the team left Colombo where they were blessed by saffron-robed Buddhist monks.
"I am satisfied with the security arranged for us and I am happy to lead my team to Pakistan. We hope to give a good fight to our very strong hosts.

Sri Lanka National team left SLC head quarters this morning to embark on their tour to Pakistan. Sri Lanka will play a three-match ODI series in Karachi and three T20Is in Lahore. #PAKvSL pic.twitter.com/tiaTSxgpNh
— Sri Lanka Cricket ?? (@OfficialSLC) September 24, 2019
ODI skipper Lahiru Thirimanne said he also had no concerns and they had been given assurances of a very high degree of protection in Pakistan, usually reserved for visits by heads of state.
Sri Lanka's cricket board received the all-clear from the defence ministry last week to go ahead with the tour after establishing that there was no threat.</Description><PublishedDate>9/24/2019 1:00:38 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Pakistan’s unluckiest cricketer: He doesn't give up</Title><Description>If there was a list of Pakistan’s unluckiest cricketers, left-handed batter Fawad Alam — without any doubt — would be on the top; but he proudly maintained that he does not "let disappointment come in my way".
Fawad has been performing continuously, scoring runs in the domestic tournaments but it seems like all of his efforts are going in vain. He made an unbeaten 100 off 138 deliveries, scoring his 31st first-class century, for Sindh during Saturday's Quaid-e-Azam Trophy match against Khyber Pakhtunkhwa (KP).
The cricketer now has 11,559 runs in 247 innings, of which 42 were unbeaten. Sunday's century took his career average to a mammoth 56.38, which is fourth best among all the cricketers making their first-class debut in current century.
Better than Fawad, however, were India's Hanuma Vihari with 60.30, Mosaddek Hossain of Bangladesh with 59.86, and Australia’s Steve Smith at 59.05.
While the left-handed batter has only played three Test matches for Pakistan, with his last appearance being in 2009, other players have received enough share of international cricket. However, the 33-year-old Karachiite said he did not consider himself to be an unlucky cricketer just because he was not picked.
“My job is inside the ground, not outside. Ups and downs are part of life. You can’t get everything on your way every time. You just don’t have to give up," he said. "I have seen more downs than ups but thankfully that has made me even stronger and I always try to keep my chin up.”
A question that has become a regular for Fawad every time he speaks to the media pertains to how he is not included in the national team. But, every time, he has the same answer.
When, on Sunday, he was asked the same question, he said: “My job is to perform in middle. Why I am not picked is a question for the selectors.”
But how long Fawad should continue doing the same job and how long before his scores and performances are answered?
This is a question that remains unanswered. Needless to say, it frustrates him as well.
“Frustration is usually natural, you usually get sad when your work is not noticed,” he said. “But I don’t let disappointment come in my way.
"If I was thinking about injustices and everything, then my career would have ended three years ago,” he said.
“This is part and parcel of our life, a player can’t define why he is not being picked, only selector can tell you this. My job is to do whatever I can, in middle and keep knocking on doors.
"Rest is up to the selectors,” he noted.</Description><PublishedDate>9/23/2019 1:14:31 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Ramiz asks Pakistani team to play fearless cricket against Sri Lanka</Title><Description>Ramiz Raja believes the upcoming series against Sri Lanka will be ideal for the Pakistan team to gain confidence.
Pakistan and Sri Lanka will play three ODIs and as many T20s in Karachi and Lahore later this month.
Pakistan and Sri Lanka are scheduled to play three ODIs in Karachi on September 27, September 29 and October 2 and three T20I starting in Lahore on October 5, October 7 and October 9.
Raja who represented Pakistan during the 1980s and the 1990s said this was the time for Pakistan team to come out of the mediocre approach and play fearless cricket and experiment variety of shots.
We cannot become a great team or player if we won't play fearless cricket with a different approach, he said while talking on his YouTube channel.
Ramiz said the Sri Lankan team touring Pakistan was an average one and the green-shirts must not take the pressure.
Under23 and Under19 players should have been included in the series as it was the best opportunity for players to gain confidence," he said.
Raja was of the view that there was new team management and a new season has begun, therefore Pakistan team must go in the series with a new approach.
Pakistan team management and captain's different approach would be seen in the series if the team wins with big margins," he said.
He added there was a need to revamp the club and school level cricket.</Description><PublishedDate>9/22/2019 3:32:08 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Bangladesh beats Afghanistan by 4 wickets, Shakib smacked unbeaten half-century</Title><Description>Shakib Al Hasan smacked an unbeaten half-century as Bangladesh ended their four-match losing streak to Afghanistan in Twenty20 internationals with a four-wicket win in their final league match of the tri-nation tournament in Chittagong on Saturday.
Shakib hit an unbeaten 70 off 45 balls to guide Bangladesh to 139-6 in 19 overs after young off-spinner Afif Hossain led the bowling effort with 2-9, helping the home side restrict Afghanistan to 138-7 in 20 overs.
In pursuit of a modest target, Bangladesh wobbled at the start as openers Liton Das (four) and Najmul Hossain (five) both fell cheaply before Shakib put on 58 runs with Mushfiqur Rahim to steady the innings.
Mushfiqur made 26 off 25 balls, but not before he was dropped by substitute fielder Najib Tarakai off Mohammad Nabi on 14.
Medium pacer Karim Janat dismissed Mushfiqur in the 11th over before a floodlight disruption enabled Afghanistan´s bowlers to regroup.
Rashid Khan struck twice after the delay and debutant Naveen-ul-Haq also claimed a wicket as Bangladesh lost Mahmudullah (six), Sabbir Rahman (one) and Afif (two) in quick succession to slide to 104-6.
Mosaddek Hossain cut Rashid late for a brilliant boundary to ease some pressure on the home side before Shakib struck the Afghanistan skipper for a four and six in consecutive balls to take Bangladesh close.
"If you look at the last few months, we haven´t been up to the mark in T20s. We´re working on it. The bowlers bowled well on the wicket," Shakib said after the match.
"We needed someone to bat through the innings. And luckily today it was my day," he said.
Mosaddek, who was unbeaten on 19, chipped Naveen at mid-on for two runs in the last ball of the penultimate over to complete only Bangladesh´s second T20 win against Afghanistan.
Earlier, Afif swung the momentum Bangladesh´s way with his double strike in the 10th over of Afghanistan´s innings after Hazratullah Zazai made 47 runs off 35 balls, putting on 75 runs with Rahmanullah Gurbaz in the opening stand.
A wicket apiece for Mohammad Saifuddin, Shafiul Islam, Shakib and Mustafizur Rahman left Afghanistan in disarray before Shafiqullah´s 23 off 17 balls gave them a glimmer of hope.
Afghanistan and Bangladesh had already qualified for Tuesday´s final in Dhaka after winning two of their previous three matches in a competition that also featured Zimbabwe.
"Best things are that it´s happened in the group stages. We have to restart and do the basics right for the final," Rashid said.</Description><PublishedDate>9/21/2019 11:37:49 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Pakistan squad announced for Sri Lanka ODI series</Title><Description>The Pakistan Cricket Board on Saturday announced a 16-member squad for the upcoming series against Sri Lanka.
Abid Ali, Iftikhar Ahmed, Mohammad Nawaz, Mohammad Rizwan and Usman Shinwari earned recalls to the team while Hasan Ali missed out his place in the side due to a back spasm.
Mohammad Hafeez, Ahmed Shahzad and Umar Akmal also miss out.
The squad for the three T20Is against Sri Lanka in Lahore will be announced during the one-day series. Until then, the other players in the probables camp will continue to train at the NCA.
Addressing a press conference Head Coach and Chief Selector Misbah-ul-Haq said, “After thorough discussions with the members of the selection committee and meticulous planning, I feel we have put together the best possible squad."
He added, “These are the only 50-over matches we play this season and we want to make their optimum use. Over the course of my cricketing career, I have realised there are no easy games and there are no easy opponents in cricket."
Misbah added a season-opening series is crucial for setting the tone. "It is extremely important that we produce solid performances and have favourable results as it will build the confidence of our players and help in carrying the momentum Down Under," he noted.
“The five boys, who have been recalled, were straightforward selections. Iftikhar Ahmed is a batsman who can also bowl off-spin and provides the captain with necessary bowling depth as Sri Lanka boasts a few left-handers in their ranks. Mohammad Nawaz has been performing well in domestic matches. Despite their strong performances, Mohammad Rizwan, Usman Shinwari and Abid Ali were unlucky to miss out the World Cup squad," he said.
“This is, however, a perfect opportunity for these players to prove their mettle in international cricket and cement their place in the one-day side,” Misbah added.
Sri Lanka will tour Pakistan to play three ODIs and three T20I matches from September 27 to October 9.
ODI squad 
Sarfaraz Ahmed (captain), Babar Azam, Shadab Khan, Abdi Ali, Asif Ali, Fakhar Zaman, Usman Shinwari, Haris Sohail, Muhammad Hasnain, Iftikhar Ahmed, Imad Wasim, Imam-ul-Haq, Mohammad Amir, Mohammad Nawaz, Wahab Riaz and Mohammad Rizwan</Description><PublishedDate>9/21/2019 10:54:34 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Sri Lanka Cricket Board gives go ahead with Pakistan tour</Title><Description>Sri Lanka's cricket board Thursday said it will go ahead with its tour of Pakistan.
Sri Lanka Cricket Secretary Mohan de Silva said they received the all-clear from the defence ministry to leave for Pakistan on Tuesday.
"We have the green light from the defence ministry," de Silva told AFP.
"The tour is on as we planned. I myself and our office bearers will also be accompanying the team."
Reports last week of a possible terror attack were referred to the defence ministry for investigation.
The Sri Lanka team was the target of an attack during a Test match in Pakistan's Lahore in March 2009, with six players injured when gunmen attacked their bus.
Since the attack, a majority of international teams have refused to tour the South Asian country.
Sri Lanka's first match in Lahore after that was one T20 game against Pakistan in October 2017.
De Silva visited Pakistan last month along with a security consultant to check out the arrangements made by the hosts.
"They have promised security reserved for a head of state," de Silva said.
The six-match tour, due to start on September 27, was put on hold last week after the Sri Lanka prime minister's office warned the board it had unspecified information about a possible attack against its players.
The Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB) said it was not aware of any information relating to the safety of the Sri Lankan team, but reiterated its commitment to providing security.
Ten senior players opted out of the tour citing security concerns.
Sri Lanka has already announced two squads for the three one-day internationals and the three T20 matches.
Pakistan and Sri Lanka are scheduled to play three ODI matches at Karachi’s National Stadium on September 27, 29 and October 2. Three T20Is will take place at Lahore’s Gaddafi Stadium on October 5, 7 and 9.
Sri Lanka will host Pakistan for two World Test Championships in late December.</Description><PublishedDate>9/19/2019 6:30:40 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Former South Africa Test player Kyle Abbott took 17 wickets in Hampshire’s County Championship</Title><Description>Former South Africa Test player Kyle Abbott took 17 wickets in Hampshire’s County Championship win over title-chasing Somerset — the best figures in first-class cricket for 63 years.
The paceman’s match return of 17-86 is the best ever for Hamphire and the best overall since England spinner Jim Laker took 19-90 against Australia in 1956.
Abbott, 32, had taken 9-40 in the first innings and replicated his incredible fast bowling with a remarkable 8-46, the Championship’s first 17-wicket haul for 80 years.
Somerset, who needed 281 to win, were skittled for just 144 in their second innings on Wednesday.
The 136-run defeat, Somerset’s third loss of the season, means they will need to beat their title rivals Essex at Taunton next week if they are to win the Championship for the first time. Essex are on the brink of victory against Surrey.</Description><PublishedDate>9/19/2019 11:47:57 AM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>COAS General Bajwa meets boxer Muhammad Waseem</Title><Description>Chief of Army Staff (COAS) General Qamar Javed Bajwa met Pakistani boxer Muhammad Waseem in Rawalpindi on Wednesday. COAS Gen Bajwa assured the boxer of full support for his boxing engagements.
Waseem, 32, is Pakistan’s most prominent pugilist and had an unbeaten record until he copped his first defeat against South Africa’s Moruti Mthalane last year.
The trajectory of Chaman-born’s career, however, has been bogged by financial issues. Last week, he knocked out a Filipino opponent in record time during a professional bout.

COAS met boxer Muhammad Waseem at his office. Congratulated him for the recent achievement bringing honour for the country. “Talent like you is our pride, we are here to support youngsters like you having potential and positive energy”, COAS. pic.twitter.com/2sweNyY1AH
— DG ISPR (@OfficialDGISPR) September 18, 2019
"COAS met boxer Muhammad Waseem at his office. Congratulated him for the recent achievement bringing honour for the country. Talent like you is our pride, we are here to support youngsters like you having potential and positive energy, COAS," tweeted the DG ISPR.
Earlier in September, star boxer Muhammad Waseem had returned to winning in spectacular style by knocking out his Filipino opponent Conrado within 82 seconds of the opening round of a match.
By doing so, Waseem, who had suffered the sole defeat of his pro career last year in a world title bout, bounced back and improved his professional boxing record to 9-0 ( KOs).
What makes Waseem’s victory even more impressive is that he floored Tanamor with a barrage of left hooks and body shots. The victory was his first fight since last year's title bout, which he lost on points.</Description><PublishedDate>9/18/2019 11:09:00 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>A player after making it to the national team cannot learn the way a youngster can: Javed Miandad</Title><Description>The best Sri Lankan players opting out of their upcoming tour of Pakistan should not be a problem for the hosts according to former Pakistan captain Javed Miandad.
Sri Lanka are scheduled to play three One-day Internationals and as many T20s in Karachi and Lahore respectively with the first ODI on Sept 27.
However, citing security fears, Sri Lanka’s top players, namely T20 skipper Lasith Malinga, former captains Angelo Mathews and Dinesh Chandimal, Suranga Lakmal, Dimuth Karunaratne, Thisara Perera, Akila Dhananjaya, Dhananjaya de Silva, Kusal Perera and Niroshan Dickwella have decided not to visit Pakistan for the limited-overs games.
“It does not matter which Sri Lankan players visit and Pakistan must only look to put up their best performances regardless of the visitors’ squad quality,” Miandad told APP.
Miandad, however, believed that Sri Lanka Cricket should take action against their players who prioritise foreign T20 leagues over international duty.
“International matches should be the top priority for the players and SLC should penalise the ones who have opted out of the Pakistan series,” the 62-year-old said.
Miandad said the series will help Pakistan make a good start to their international cricket calendar which also includes series against Australia and Bangla­desh. He said playing Sri Lanka at home will give Pakistani players confidence.
The right-hander, who amassed 8,832 runs in 124 Tests for Pakistan, said Pakistan batsman should try to aim higher and improve their averages. He urged them to try and get 200 runs whenever they make a century.
“This will help them improve their mentality,” said Miandad.
The Karachi-born legend said the Pakistan Cricket Board should use former players to work with blossoming cricketers at the grassroots level. Miandad also urged the board to work on school and club cricket.
“A player after making it to the national team cannot learn the way a youngster can,” he said.</Description><PublishedDate>9/16/2019 2:01:18 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>We will have to change our mindset and play aggressive cricket in Australia says Yasir Shah</Title><Description>Yasir Shah, a leading Test leg-spin bowler said that they have to change their mindset and play aggressive cricket in Australia He was talking to the media after the end of first day’s play of the Quaid-e-Azam Trophy at the UBL Sports Complex. “We will have to change our mindset and play aggressive cricket in Australia because you get in trouble if you don’t play on the offensive there,” said Shah. He also said that the spinners will have their work cut out in their tour of Australia later this&amp;#8230;</Description><PublishedDate>9/15/2019 6:07:38 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Sarfaraz retained as Pakistan captain, Babar named vice-captain</Title><Description>The Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB) said Friday it was retaining Sarfaraz Ahmed as the captain of the Pakistani team, whereas Babar Azam was named the vice-captain for the upcoming Sri Lanka series.
The series, wherein Sarfaraz will lead Pakistan, comprises three one-day international (ODI) and three Twenty20 international (T20I) matches against Sri Lanka and is slated to be held from September 27 to October 9.
PCB chairperson Ehsan Mani confirmed the appointments, the cricket regulatory authority said in a press release issued Friday. The decisions were made "following recommendations made by Pakistan head coach and chief selector Misbah-ul-Haq and the PCB Cricket Committee".
In this regard, Sarfaraz said he was "humbled and honoured" for the extension and added: "I have enjoyed captaining the Pakistan cricket team and look forward to improve my leadership qualities under the new set-up of Misbah-ul-Haq who also has a proven record as captain."
Highlighting having played cricket under Misbah, the chief selector, Sarfaraz further noted: “I think we will make a good combination, which will contribute to improved performances of the side across all formats.
“I am aware we have not done justice to our potential in ODIs, which has disappointed us as well as our fans. I am hopeful we will be able to turn things around in the coming season and in this relation.
"I remain committed to stepping up to the challenge with my performances and captaincy. I have complete faith in my team, which has time and again shown talent, class and charisma it possesses.
"The only thing missing has been consistency, which Misbah and I would like to focus and improve across all departments of the game. I assure all our fans we will not leave any stone unturned in our preparations for the forthcoming assignments and will do our best to translate these preparations into solid performances,” the captain added.
Terming Sarfaraz "an experienced campaigner", Mani, the PCB chair, said the captain "has excelled and improved as a leader with every match".
He noted: "I have complete faith in his abilities and I am confident he will continue to blossom under Misbah’s wings. We have appointed Babar Azam as Sarfaraz’s vice-captain. This is part of Babar’s gradual development as a future captain and in line with our strategy of introducing a succession plan across the board so that there are no gaps.
"I am hopeful the trio of Misbah, Sarfaraz and Babar will do well for Pakistan cricket,” he added.
Misbah-ul-Haq, on the other hand, congratulated Sarfaraz and Babar on their appointments, saying: "Both are one of the most talented and exceptionally gifted Pakistan cricketers and thoroughly deserve these assignments.
“Consistency backed up by good performance has been my yardstick for recommending Sarfaraz as captain. Furthermore, I think I am better placed to get the best out of Sarfaraz as I know him better than most of the cricketers as he has played most of his cricket under my captaincy.
"I have always been an admirer of his commitment and the energy he brings to the side.
“I have emphasised on changing the dressing room culture and mind-set of the players to achieve better results, and I believe Sarfaraz is a perfect fit to help me attain these objectives.
“In the past couple of weeks, Sarfaraz and I have worked together on certain areas of his cricket that will enhance his overall performance. Both of us realise it is a performance-oriented world and we are expected to give our best every time we take the field.
"I look forward to working with him and hope we will succeed in changing the outlook of the Pakistan cricket team,” he noted.
Squad and training
Separately, 19 players likely to be added to the team for the Sri Lanka series would be announced on Monday. The training camp, on the other hand, "will commence at the National Cricket Academy from Wednesday, 18 September", the PCB said.
It added: "The 16-player ODI and T20I squads will be named on Monday, 23 September."
Sarfaraz was appointed as the captain of the Pakistan team for the T20Is in April 2016 before being promoted as the ODI captain in early 2017. Subsequently, he was named captain across all formats.
He has has captained the Pakistan team in 13 Test, 48 ODI, and 34 T20I matches, winning four, 26, and 29 matches, respectively.
However, Babar Azam — ranked 16th in Tests, third in ODIs, and No. 1 in T20Is — captained Pakistan earlier in the ICC U19 Cricket World Cup 2012.
Babar also featured in the ICC U19 Cricket World Cup 2010 before entering the international cricket scene in 2015 and has since regularly featured in all formats.</Description><PublishedDate>9/13/2019 11:20:57 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Andrew Strauss appointed ECB’s cricket committee chairman</Title><Description>Former England captain Andrew Strauss is back in the England and Wales Cricket Board (ECB) as cricket committee chairman and will drive the development of the game at all levels as part of his new role.
The 42-year-old, who was knighted on Tuesday, stepped down as ECB’s director of cricket last year to support his late wife Ruth’s cancer battle and was replaced by former England spinner Ashley Giles.
“The ECB have been a vital source of support over an extremely difficult year,” Strauss was quoted as saying by the BBC. “It’s a real pleasure to return… I’m extremely passionate about developing and growing cricket in England and Wales.”
In his previous position, Strauss appointed coach Trevor Bayliss, who guided the national team to their maiden 50-overs World Cup title in July.
“I’ve seen first-hand how this summer of cricket has inspired more people to fall in love with the sport and I can’t wait to help build on its success,” Strauss added.</Description><PublishedDate>9/13/2019 11:33:02 AM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Wahab to take indefinite break from Test Cricket</Title><Description>Left-arm fast-bowler Wahab Riaz confirmed on Thursday that he has withdrawn from the Quaid-e-Azam Trophy and will take an indefinite break from red-ball cricket.
Wahab Riaz said: “After reviewing my past couple of years’ performances in red-ball cricket and the upcoming limited overs cricket, I have decided to take time off from first-class cricket."
The bowler said that during this period, he will like to focus on 50-over and 20-over cricket, and continue to access his fitness for the longer version of the game.
"At a stage I feel I cannot only return but also perform with the red-ball, I would make myself available," he said.
Wahab Riaz also posted on Twitter about his decision to take a break from red-ball cricket.
“The PCB had been trying to convince me to pursue my career with red-ball, but today I met them to convey my decision. I am grateful for their understanding and support," stated the bowler.</Description><PublishedDate>9/12/2019 9:09:27 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Cricketer Sana Mir to receive Asia Game Changers Award</Title><Description>Former captain of Pakistan’s women cricket team Sana Mir has been selected for prestigious Asia Game Changers Award by the Asia Society.
According to a statement by Asia Society, Mir will receive the award along with five other women who have excelled in their respective fields.
The award ceremony will be held in New York City on October 24, 2019.
“Asia Society is honouring Sana Mir, recognized as one of the world’s greatest cricket players and former captain of Pakistan’s national team, who has championed women’s participation in this male-dominated sport,” the statement from the Asia Society read.
The Asia Society annually honours game-changing leaders from a broad geographic range and varied backgrounds; this year marks the first time that all of the honorees are women.
"Our 2019 Asia Game Changers are women who have truly championed gender equality while making enormous contributions to society and social structures within their home countries. They are inspiring agents of change who are building a better world — for women and for everyone — by changing the rules, changing the game, and challenging all of us to follow their lead." Asia Society President and CEO Josette Sheeran said.
According to the Asia Society website, Mir has been selected for this prestigious award for excelling at one of the world’s most popular sports and inspiring millions of girls — on and off the field.
“In a country where many women still struggle for basic rights, Mir’s success has been a lodestar. Unwilling to simply rest on her laurels, Mir is an outspoken advocate for women’s rights, working to change attitudes about women’s participation in the traditionally male-dominated sport of cricket — and beyond.”
“An avid social media user who is followed by hundreds of thousands, Mir employs her platform to advocate for everything from compulsory cricket programs for schoolgirls to an end to body-shaming advertisement,” it added.
 </Description><PublishedDate>9/12/2019 8:57:47 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Sri Lanka announce ODI, T20 squads for Pakistan tour</Title><Description>The Sri Lanka cricket board has announced its squads for its upcoming One-Day International (ODI) and T20i series against Pakistan.
In a press statement on Wednesday, Sri Lanka Cricket said approval for the squads was given by "the Minister of Telecommunication, Foreign Employment and Sports Honorable Harin Fernando to take part in the forthcoming Sri Lanka tour of Pakistan".
Sri Lanka will tour Pakistan to play three ODIs and three T20i matches from September 27 to October 9.
The 15-member ODI squad includes Lahiru Thirimanne (Captain), Danushka Gunathilaka, Sadeera Samarawickrama, Avishka Fernando, Oshada Fernando, Shehan Jayasuriya, Dasun Shanaka, Minod Bhanuka, Angelo Perera, Wanindu Hasaranga, Lakshan Sandakan, Nuwan Pradeep, Isuru Udana, Kasun Rajitha, and Lahiru Kumara.
Dasun Shanaka (Captain), Danushka Gunathilaka, Sadeera Samarawickrama, Avishka Fernando, Oshada Fernando, Shehan Jayasuriya, Angelo Perera, Bhanuka Rajapaksha, Minod Bhanuka, Lahiru Madushanka, Wanindu Hasaranga, Lakshan Sandakan, Isuru Udana, Nuwan Pradeep, Kasun Rajitha, and Lahiru Kumara are part of the 16-member T20i squad.
The announcement comes days after at least 10 Sri Lankan players, including T20 skipper Lasith Malinga and former captains Angelo Mathews and Thisara Perera, pulled out of the upcoming tour of Pakistan citing security concerns.
The other seven who opted out were Niroshan Dickwella, Kusal Perera, Dhananjaya de Silva, Akila Dananjaya, Suranga Lakmal, Dinesh Chandimal, and Dimuth Karunaratne.
The Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB), however, said the Pakistan-Sri Lanka series would be held according to schedule, and that "it should not make a difference if senior [Sri Lankan] players come or not." It said that the cricketers opting out of the series was an internal matter for the SLC, which would choose the players for the series.</Description><PublishedDate>9/11/2019 7:56:44 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Pakistan-India tensions throw women's cricket series into jeopardy</Title><Description>The recent tensions between Pakistan and India have also spilled into the world of women’s cricket with the upcoming series between Pakistan and Indian women cricket team in jeopardy.
As part of the ICC Championship, Pakistan and India are scheduled to play a series from July to November to be hosted by India.
The Indian cricket board has sought permission from the government to host the series however, the Indian government is yet to give an answer back.
According to sources in the Pakistan Cricket Board, Pakistan will not contact India for the series, since India is responsible for hosting the series.
The source added, no contact has been made from the India side over the series either.
In the past, the Indian women's cricket team refused to play a series with Pakistan, despite Pakistan offering to play the series at a neutral venue.
Due to India's refusal to play the series, Pakistan was awarded the points.
An International Cricket Council spokesman said the series between the two countries and it was the responsibility of the member countries to arrange the series.
The spokesman added, if the issue of points table came to ICC, it will be resolved.</Description><PublishedDate>9/11/2019 1:18:07 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Funeral prayers held for  legend Abdul Qadir</Title><Description>The funeral prayer of legendary wrist-spinner Abdul Qadir was held in the provincial capital on Saturday.
A large number of people, including cricketers and government officials, attended his funeral.
The former test cricketer had passed away yesterday after he suffered a cardiac attack in Lahore.Qadir represented Pakistan in 67 Tests and 104 ODIs between 1977 and 1993 and was widely recognized as the foremost leg spinner of his times.
The 64-year old Abdul Qadir represented Pakistan in two World Cups (1983 and 1987). He also captained the Pakistan cricket team in five ODIs.
He later served as chief selector for the Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB).
 </Description><PublishedDate>9/7/2019 6:45:08 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Malinga took four wickets in four balls</Title><Description>Sri Lanka's Lasith Malinga Friday became the first bowler in Twenty20 internationals to claim 100 wickets, achieving the feat in the third match against New Zealand in Kandy.
Malinga, who surpassed Pakistan spinner Shahid Afridi's tally of 97 scalps to become the leading T20 wicket-taker on Sunday, bowled Colin Munro to get a century of wickets in his 76th match.
The 36-year-old speedster went on to complete a hat-trick and took four wickets in four balls. Hamish Rutherford, Colin de Grandhomme and Ross Taylor followed Munro to the pavilion.</Description><PublishedDate>9/6/2019 11:25:55 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem><NewsItem><Title>Former Pakistani Spin legend Abdul Qadir passes away</Title><Description>Former Pakistan cricketer and spin legend Abdul Qadir Khan passed away in Lahore on Friday, cricketer Kamran Akmal confirmed.
Akmal, whose brother is married to Qadir's daughter, said the legendary cricketer passed away due to cardiac arrest.
The 67-year-old was born in Lahore in 1955. He was regarded one of the best leg-spinners of his time, taking 236 wickets in 67 Test matches and 132 wickets in just 104 One Day Internationals (ODIs).
He later served as chief selector for the Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB) as well as a match commentator.</Description><PublishedDate>9/6/2019 10:48:25 PM +05:00</PublishedDate><NewsChannel>SuchTv</NewsChannel></NewsItem></NewsFeed>